[{"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8f4", "question": "What do you have if you are suffering from circadian dysrhythmia?", "answer": "Jet lag", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe8ad9801dd7bf43be5e77b", "question": "The BLAT variation of the BLT sandwich adds what ingredient?", "answer": "Avocado", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58c8a67690aac110e416707d", "question": "In \"Alice in Wonderland\", who did Alice see taking tea under a tree?", "answer": "Mad Hatter and March Hare", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae15", "question": "What English legal document was signed in 1215?", "answer": "Magna Carta", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ae866977f28483af1e7fdd4", "question": "What is the name of the musician best known for his 1993 song \"What is Love\"?", "answer": "Haddaway", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab35", "question": "Which ocean is Zanzibar located in?", "answer": "Indian", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c646", "question": "What is the name of Earth's first artificial satellite?", "answer": "Sputnik", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a11f", "question": "Who won an Academy Award in 1970 for directing the film \"Midnight Cowboy\"?", "answer": "John Schlesinger", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe1f17b145fb29466707393", "question": "What does the Italian term \"Al Dente\" mean in regards to pasta?", "answer": "To the teeth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbea", "question": "Jean Paul Gaultier was hired as an assistant to what popular designer?", "answer": "Pierre Cardin", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e0f", "question": "What 1993 film's title character has the first name Euphegenia?", "answer": "Mrs. Doubtfire's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "596dfe159616e6c6d4eba4fb", "question": "What island does the Statue of Liberty stand on?", "answer": "Liberty Island", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b63a", "question": "Which company was the first to offer a Valentine's Day chocolate box?", "answer": "Cadbury", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b909", "question": "What video game got its name from a Japanese mistranslation of \"King Kong\"?", "answer": "Donkey Kong", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe909e001dd7bf43be5e892", "question": "What was Mary Anning famous for in the 19th century?", "answer": "Collecting fossils", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b61f", "question": "What iPod was the first without a screen or a scroll wheel?", "answer": "The iPod Shuffle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c647", "question": "On the pH scale, which number represents \"Neutral?\"", "answer": "7", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338906", "question": "Who wrote the music for the stage version of \"Billy Elliot\"?", "answer": "Elton John", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c198", "question": "In what sort of landscape would you find an erg?", "answer": "Desert", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7f1", "question": "What chemical element has been added to table salt since 1924, to help prevent goiter?", "answer": "Iodine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338da1", "question": "What author created the character of Tom Hagen?", "answer": "Mario Puzo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caad", "question": "What does an otologist study?", "answer": "Ears", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a277", "question": "When was actress and pin-up model, Betty Grable born?", "answer": "1916", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3d2", "question": "Which country hosted the 1982 FIFA World Cup?", "answer": "Spain", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fdfbdc1003d27d341092bca", "question": "What is the only US state with a Spanish motto?", "answer": "Montana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa76", "question": "Lilongwe is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Malawi", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c878", "question": "What's the world's largest predatory fish?", "answer": "The great white shark", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5a9e95a47ccba3ffe45786e2", "question": "Who wrote the opera \"Rigoletto\"?", "answer": "Giuseppe Verdi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "600399ab57a0e35c43f8389e", "question": "What artist first achieved notoriety through graffiti epigrams?", "answer": "Jean-Michel Basquiat\u00a0first achieved notoriety as part of SAMO, an informal graffiti duo who wrote enigmatic epigrams.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339971", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", how many children do Apu and Manjula have?", "answer": "Eight", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339658", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", why did Bart and Homer have to work at the carnival?", "answer": "Bart wrecked Hitler's car", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5937ed1e08d98002fdd633c4", "question": "The 1976 Summer Olympics were held in which city?", "answer": "Montreal", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58ab95d686faa38a764be519", "question": "Under what name was the AC Cobra sold in the US?", "answer": "Shelby Cobra", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a35a", "question": "What is the most sacred river of India?", "answer": "The Ganges", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394d8", "question": "Who was Kevin Arnold's some time girlfriend on \"The Wonder Years\"?", "answer": "Winnie Copper", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beef", "question": "If a dish is served pomontier, what does it contain?", "answer": "Potatoes", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe65ed21f3c0ead6880d630", "question": "What does the French dessert B\u00fbche de No\u00ebl represent?", "answer": "Yule log", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b47e", "question": "What two countries fought in the Battle of the Plains of Abraham?", "answer": "Great Britain and France", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5b1", "question": "What must a mole do every four hours or it will die?", "answer": "Eat", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e47", "question": "What athlete had a part in the movie \"There's Something About Mary\"?", "answer": "Brett Favre", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be0a", "question": "In 1997, what Oscar winner was replaced by Sarah Ferguson as Weight Watchers' spokesperson?", "answer": "Lynn Redgrave", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5f16516af9b80650dbe7f93c", "question": "Which Mormon founded Salt Lake City?", "answer": "Brigham Young", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b91", "question": "What daily comic strip features occasional visits from Bob the Dinosaur, \"king of the wedgies\"?", "answer": "Dilbert", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b34b", "question": "Which Cambodian party was Pol Pot the leader of?", "answer": "Khmer Rouge", "category": "history"}, {"id": "600cc2f26de0eb824d4052e8", "question": "What South American country is a former Dutch colony?", "answer": "Suriname", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392ab", "question": "What 1972 movie revolves around the happenings at the Kit-Kat Klub?", "answer": "Cabaret", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a9e966c7ccba3ffe45786ed", "question": "In which country would you find the Tokaj wine region?", "answer": "Hungary", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133888e", "question": "What is Dennis the Menace's last name?", "answer": "Mitchell", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ccf7965b37b32637bdc44be", "question": "What shape is a wombat\u2019s fecal matter?", "answer": "Cubic", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd2a", "question": "Who opened her first school, Rome's Casa dei Bambini, in 1907?", "answer": "Maria Montessori", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c3d", "question": "What year did actor Anthony Hopkins become a naturalized citizen of the US?", "answer": "2000", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea7e09ff048f679a45ac06", "question": "Ataxophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Disorder or untidiness", "category": "science"}, {"id": "592203e2a4edfd43a087ade4", "question": "The 1999 film adaptation of \"The Green Mile\" starred whom as Paul Edgecomb?", "answer": "Tom Hanks", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a252", "question": "What 1980s TV show starred Bruce Willis in a detective agency?", "answer": "Moonlighting", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac15", "question": "The Union of the Comoros is located on the northern end of which water channel?", "answer": "Mozambique Channel", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab72", "question": "What is the capital of Bangladesh?", "answer": "Dhaka", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5bd05b4540191c55fd523fb1", "question": "Which person is most often associated with SpaceX and Tesla?", "answer": "Elon Musk", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff14580b0ee8c595b6d39ba", "question": "What was the name of Don Quixote's horse?", "answer": "Rocinante", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9cf", "question": "What is the capital of the US state New Jersey?", "answer": "Trenton", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe4edf406d333868d34d771", "question": "The musical score for Hitchcock's \"Psycho\" uses which instrument exclusively?", "answer": "Stringed instruments", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf6a", "question": "What egyptian object is also known as \"The Key to the Nile\"?", "answer": "Ankh", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe73482eec85e375820b236", "question": "Who was the first president to pardon a turkey?", "answer": "Harry Truman", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be6a", "question": "What is Indianapolis Speedway also known as?", "answer": "The Brickyard", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bc1", "question": "Who was adviser to Odysseus whose name is now synonymous with a trusted councilor?", "answer": "Mentor", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396bd", "question": "U2's Paul Hewson is better known by which nickname?", "answer": "Bono", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c903", "question": "What is an emasculated stallion called?", "answer": "Gelding", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3bb", "question": "Which Renaissance City was severely flooded in November 1966?", "answer": "Florence", "category": "history"}, {"id": "597743a3284458f1d785442a", "question": "Who wrote the book \"Great Expectations\"?", "answer": "Charles Dickens", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaa6", "question": "What is the easternmost state in the contiguous US?", "answer": "Maine", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca51", "question": "What fruit is \"Citrus grandis\"?", "answer": "Pomelo", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe7704eeec85e375820b2f7", "question": "What republic claims to be the world's oldest surviving republic?", "answer": "San Marino", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b5b", "question": "Which fairytale character slept for 20 years?", "answer": "Rip Van Winkle", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59cdb12065ff7d326b622a66", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Curium?", "answer": "Cm", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d80", "question": "Who was the real-life model for the character of Matthew Harrison Brady in the novel \"Inherit the Wind\"?", "answer": "William Jennings Bryan", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb44", "question": "At what university did Tiger Woods play collegiate golf for two years before turning pro?", "answer": "Stanford", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133915a", "question": "Who is Bugs Bunny's archenemy?", "answer": "Elmer J. Fudd", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a9a", "question": "In the children?s nursery rhyme, what comes next after ?Mary, Mary quite contrary??", "answer": "How does your garden grow?", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3a2", "question": "What is the official language of Egypt?", "answer": "Arabic", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5e91065ed7247dfc0fa00315", "question": "At what point does hydrogen turn from a solid to a liquid?", "answer": "Approximately 14 K, -259\u00b0 C, or -434\u00b0 F.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5da855f01aec824685d88d04", "question": "What is the most common street name in the United States?", "answer": "Park, according to a Washington Post study", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe65674ae7e414034b5aec9", "question": "Which country had an Orange Revolution between 2004 and 2005?", "answer": "Ukraine", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0fb", "question": "What major political scandal of the Harding administration involved a naval oil reserve on public land in Wyoming?", "answer": "The Teapot Dome Scandal", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fde5297c6c6b019850c9a97", "question": "What was the motto of the Hitler Youth in World War II?", "answer": "Blood and Honor", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7c6", "question": "In what country is the holy city of Mecca?", "answer": "Saudi Arabia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe938d96bd93ce3a4e5f688", "question": "What branch of science is concerned with the interaction between matter and electromagnetic radiation?", "answer": "Spectroscopy", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394b4", "question": "Who played the role of Tom in the TV show \"Rich Man, Poor Man\"?", "answer": "Nick Nolte", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600f7179a9e54d890926f6e1", "question": "Kersti Kaljulaid was 46 years old when she became the youngest president ever elected to lead which country?", "answer": "Estonia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5a1", "question": "Which company was founded first - Apple or Microsoft?", "answer": "Microsoft", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5bc1d99ed702eaa27a66982a", "question": "Which Swedish musician sang the song \"Save Tonight\"?", "answer": "Eagle-Eye Cherry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6014c888fbde8045e48466db", "question": "What pigment makes plants green?", "answer": "Chlorophyll", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338873", "question": "What mid-day nap takes its name from the Spanish word sexta, meaning sixth?", "answer": "The siesta", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ab99adb21a8909e5c332d25", "question": "What is the Kelvin scale used to measure?", "answer": "Temperature", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5ed", "question": "Which grandmaster did Bobby Fischer defeat in 1972 and became the first American to win the world chess title?", "answer": "Boris Spassky", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396af", "question": "What actor founded the Purple Rose Theater Company in Michigan?", "answer": "Jeff Daniels", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac25", "question": "Which country borders Suriname to the west?", "answer": "Guyana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad1d", "question": "What year was Ben Franklin born in?", "answer": "1706", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60121a4763c99d48cd169b02", "question": "According to myth, who rode the flying horse named Sleipnir?", "answer": "Sleipnir, known as the fastest horses, carried Odin the All-Father through the sky, over the seas, and across the lands.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a46a", "question": "What is known as the Old Lady Of Threadneedle Street?", "answer": "The Bank of England", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "594d05b41a1c922dd1ac64a4", "question": "Who wrote the song \"Moon River\" performed by Audrey Hepburn in the film \"Breakfast at Tiffany's\"?", "answer": "Henry Mancini", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ed", "question": "What Harry Potter character has the patronus of a hare/bunny?", "answer": "Luna Lovegood", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fecdc7eec223966ae8f88f8", "question": "Who plays Marty Byrde in the TV drama series \"Ozark?\"", "answer": "Jason Bateman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a879", "question": "In what city would you find the most famous street named \"Biscayne Boulevard\"?", "answer": "Miami", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fd6", "question": "Who wrote the poem \"Anthem for Doomed Youth\"?", "answer": "Wilfred Owen", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a90", "question": "Dr. Brown's puppy in \"Back to the Future Part II\" was named after what astronomer?", "answer": "Copernicus", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b998", "question": "In the standard Monopoly game, what place will you land on if you roll 9 when on Park Avenue?", "answer": "Oriental Avenue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339804", "question": "What movie soundtrack is Eric Clapton's \"Tears in Heaven\" from?", "answer": "Rush", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd96dca23c87fd04dd15e2f", "question": "Who sculpted Mount Rushmore?", "answer": "Gutzon Borglum", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133957c", "question": "What won an Emmy for outstanding music direction in 1985?", "answer": "Christmas In Washington", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394f5", "question": "What band recorded the album \"A Night at the Opera\"?", "answer": "Queen", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5909d339bb53d1af65886510", "question": "On what date did the TV special \"A Charlie Brown Christmas\" made its debut on CBS?", "answer": "December 9, 1965", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59774232284458f1d785441e", "question": "What church in Georgia has produced the films \"Flywheel\", \"Facing the Giants\", \"Fireproof\", \"Courageous\",and \"War Room\"?", "answer": "Sherwood Baptist Church, Albany, Georgia", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff511c7ff04d658268c92ca", "question": "How did Mary Ludwig Hays earn the nickname \"Molly Pitcher\"?", "answer": "During the Battle of Monmouth, she attended to the Revolutionary soldiers by\u00a0bringing them water, often under heavy fire.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b465", "question": "Who ordered Atlanta be burned in 1864?", "answer": "General Sherman", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5feccf97ec223966ae8f88b6", "question": "What movie monster appeared in an episode of \"The Munsters\" using the name \"Uncle Gilbert\"?", "answer": "The creature from the black lagoon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd8a", "question": "Liquid Paper was invented by Bette Graham, the mother of which of the Monkees?", "answer": "Mike Nesmith", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133948c", "question": "In the movie \"Days of Thunder\", what car is Cole told to hit in his first race?", "answer": "The pace car", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59049d99cf93664eb10486af", "question": "The plane carrying what country\u2019s national rugby team crashed on Friday, October 13, 1972?", "answer": "Uruguay\u2019s", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339736", "question": "In the TV series \"Lost\", which airline's plane crashed?", "answer": "Oceanic Airlines", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5937ec2008d98002fdd633b7", "question": "Which singer's autobiography is titled \"Take It Like a Man\"?", "answer": "Boy George's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8f1cb01dd7bf43be5e808", "question": "Which Crayola color did consumers vote to save from retirement in 2003?", "answer": "Burnt sienna", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c890", "question": "What does the Mohs scale measure?", "answer": "Mineral hardness", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c013", "question": "The Venice Cup is for women only playing what?", "answer": "Bridge", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5922049aa4edfd43a087ade6", "question": "Butter bean is another name for which type of bean?", "answer": "Lima", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad7a", "question": "Who was the first man to reach the South Pole?", "answer": "Roald Amundsen", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dac", "question": "What bassist's romance with Astrid Kirchherr is the subject of the film \"Backbeat\"?", "answer": "Stu Sutcliffe", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133992e", "question": "What 1996 movie features a little boy character named Ray Boyd?", "answer": "Jerry Maguire", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febd5aa7e83c707845b2164", "question": "What was the name of the whale in the 1993 movie, \"Free Willy\"?", "answer": "Keiko", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ad9e209e748bb36357acdf8", "question": "What was Alfred Hitchcock\u2019s first American made film?", "answer": "Rebecca", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ab99d8f21a8909e5c332d41", "question": "Which playing card is known as the \"Devil's Bedpost\"?", "answer": "The Four of Clubs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc56", "question": "The necktie dates back to what century?", "answer": "17th", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a162baaf01ec323f849172b", "question": "What type of creature is a Silverback?", "answer": "A gorilla", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6ee", "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the \"Golden State\"?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339224", "question": "Who celebrated is 111th birthday during \"The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring?\"", "answer": "Bilbo Baggins", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a266", "question": "Which dance classic did the group \"The Trammps\" bring us?", "answer": "Disco Inferno", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca0b", "question": "What is the common two word name for Yucca Brevifolia?", "answer": "Joshua Tree", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58ab0ec8baab681b09292169", "question": "What is the name of the theme song of the TV show 'CSI: Cyber'?", "answer": "I Can See for Miles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea7c2dff048f679a45abf6", "question": "What was the first planet discovered by telescope?", "answer": "Uranus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58dba1a6874c93a3298b2129", "question": "What year did Jimmy Carter assume office as the 39th President of the United States?", "answer": "1977", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133917f", "question": "Who is the Kindergarten Cop?", "answer": "Arnold Schwarzenneger", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a167", "question": "Who played Sarah Conner in the 1991 film \"Terminator 2: Judgment Day\"?", "answer": "Linda Hamilton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5990f950fa5fdd6dd25324f6", "question": "What name is given to animals which only eat plants?", "answer": "Herbivores", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ba9", "question": "On the 1990's sitcom \"Roc\", what was Roc's job?", "answer": "Garbage man", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0b77de662d71a53651012", "question": "What famous philosopher poet said, \"I awoke this morning with devout thanksgiving for my friends, the old and new\"?", "answer": "Ralph Waldo Emerson", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3cc", "question": "Due to getting sick, which astronaut was replaced in the Apollo XIII mission?", "answer": "Ken Mattingly", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b97c", "question": "In the bible Zacharias and Elizabeth were the parents of whom?", "answer": "John The Baptist", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0ee", "question": "Who was the first African-American to be appointed as a US Supreme Court justice?", "answer": "Thurgood Marshall", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5eb734555e259d7869087328", "question": "Which US president went on record saying that he wished he could\u2019ve hanged his vice president during his administration?", "answer": "Andrew Jackson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a207", "question": "Harvey Lee Yeary became famous under what name?", "answer": "Lee Majors", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133982a", "question": "What type of music did Benny Goodman play?", "answer": "Jazz", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b146", "question": "In what year was Stanley sent to Africa to search for Livingstone?", "answer": "1871", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339787", "question": "What wrestler supplied the torso for the Scorpion King in the movie \"The Mummy Returns\"?", "answer": "The Rock", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "593c4a60b8198b9a2b07795b", "question": "Who played the male lead role in the film \"Terminator Salvation\"?", "answer": "Sam Worthington", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fec840fec223966ae8f87fb", "question": "What was the first TV kids show in the US?", "answer": "Howdy Doody", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5971e08e89261e916c8e09ad", "question": "What US state was \"Steak 'n Shake\" founded in?", "answer": "Illinois", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b041", "question": "In 1626, what island was purchased by Peter Minuit from the natives for goods valued at $24?", "answer": "Manhattan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339df0", "question": "What was John Woo's \"God of Guns\" film renamed for US release?", "answer": "Hard-Boiled", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe4ddb406d333868d34d707", "question": "Who was known as the \"Mad Monarch\"?", "answer": "George III", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ecae269790ded87bb38fd88", "question": "In biology, what does RNA stand for?", "answer": "Ribonucleic Acid", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fde51e6c6c6b019850c9a92", "question": "In what nation were the Dead Sea Scrolls found?", "answer": "Jordan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff51b0dff04d658268c930c", "question": "Who discovered Odysseus when he washed up on Phaeacia?", "answer": "Princess Nausicaa", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2f5", "question": "What is the largest planet in the solar system?", "answer": "Jupiter", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c302", "question": "Which media is read from the inside out, compact discs or vinyl records?", "answer": "Compact discs", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a471", "question": "What is the capital of Barbados?", "answer": "Bridgetown", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3ca", "question": "Which poisonous concoction was Socrates given to drink to carry out his death sentence?", "answer": "Hemlock", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339077", "question": "Puccini's \"Turandot\" is set in which country?", "answer": "China", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5900873f5304ceedb84e8995", "question": "What drink began in Morison's drug store in Waco, Texas in 1885?", "answer": "Dr. Pepper", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ab", "question": "Who does Emma Watson play in the Harry Potter films?", "answer": "Hermione", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59bb2911c9bff04efae6d754", "question": "In what 1967 film did Gene Hackman earn his first Oscar nomination?", "answer": "Bonnie and Clyde", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5cefc089948005ec986edcdc", "question": "Who is the third member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Haseul", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b98c", "question": "What musical instrument is played to wake up soldiers?", "answer": "Bugle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e55", "question": "What literary work inspired Manic Street Preachers' \"Patrick Bateman\" song?", "answer": "American Psycho", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c128", "question": "What year was Olympic sprinter, Don Quarrie, born?", "answer": "1951", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4bb", "question": "What year did the Comoros gain its independence from France?", "answer": "1975", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339924", "question": "Who was the host of TV\u2019s \u201cUnsolved Mysteries\u201d?", "answer": "Robert Stack", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c461", "question": "\"Ships of the desert\" are what?", "answer": "Camels", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3bd", "question": "What bird lays the smallest egg in relation to its size?", "answer": "Ostrich", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133981c", "question": "What 1996 movie features Michael Jordan returning to basketball after being influenced by a group of cartoon characters?", "answer": "Space Jam", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5af25d55b63e5727cf5a4864", "question": "\"Stay\" was a hit single for which UK band in 1992?", "answer": "Shakespeares Sister", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c530", "question": "At which pole would you find penguins?", "answer": "The South Pole", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b09b", "question": "Who was the first president to have been born after the American Revolution?", "answer": "Martin Van Buren", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339967", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what actor is the voice of Comic Book Guy?", "answer": "Hank Azaria", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7cfdf877e98cb97778a56", "question": "What is the southern most city in the contiguous U.S.?", "answer": "Key West", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "60078b7a0eee65b76b9f2669", "question": "Which dung beetle was worshipped by the ancient Egyptians?", "answer": "Scarab", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133976f", "question": "What sin does John Doe address first in Seven?", "answer": "Gluttony", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b084", "question": "What object did Ben Franklin attach to the end of a kite string to prove that lightning is electricity?", "answer": "A metal key", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015e43bfe83fe1f2a824baf", "question": "After the Battle of Kursk, the Germans did what?", "answer": "Began a lengthy retreat back to Germany.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2d4", "question": "Who played the role of Macauley Connor in the 1956 film \"High Society\"?", "answer": "Frank Sinatra", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a571", "question": "Which US state is home to North Cascades National Park?", "answer": "Washington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b655", "question": "The entrance to what New York City landmark has a pair of lion sculptures?", "answer": "Public Library", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395b5", "question": "In The Simpsons, what is the three-eyed fish named?", "answer": "Blinky", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4d4", "question": "What is the better-known name of the card game \"Twenty-One\"?", "answer": "Blackjack", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c69", "question": "What is the name of Tony Manero's dance partner in the 1977 movie \"Saturday Night Fever\"?", "answer": "Stephanie Mangano", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a971", "question": "What nation's legislative body is named The House of Lords?", "answer": "The United Kingdom", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe9f5bbff048f679a45aad8", "question": "An earthquake that measures 8 on the Richter Scale would be how many times stronger than one that measures 4 on the same scale?", "answer": "10,000 times stronger", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b230", "question": "Who did fisherman Donato Dalrymple rescue from the water on Thanksgiving Day, 1999?", "answer": "Elian Gonzalez", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339de6", "question": "What seminal L.A. punk band was discovered by Ray Manzarek of the Doors?", "answer": "X", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58dba40a874c93a3298b2142", "question": "Puccini's \"Tosca\" is based on which 1887 Victorien Sardou play?", "answer": "La Tosca", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa91", "question": "What did the Romans call Scotland?\u00a0", "answer": "Caledonia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58d115e14fea7fe947a2226b", "question": "Ernest Evans became famous under what name?", "answer": "Chubby Checker", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4b4", "question": "When did sharpshooter Annie Oakley die?", "answer": "1926", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fef5f8f6ce05a3942286e44", "question": "What was the original name of the Boston Red Sox?", "answer": "Boston Americans", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fdd60740499cffc60b84238", "question": "Which European country was occupied by Britain from 1814 until 1964?", "answer": "Malta", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388eb", "question": "What is the dot in the \"i\" called?", "answer": "A tittle", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3bf", "question": "How many stars appear on the Australian flag?", "answer": "Six", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5eb", "question": "In which country is Angel Falls located?", "answer": "Venezuela", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c400", "question": "The insect known as the yellow jacket is a type of what?", "answer": "Wasp", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8ea", "question": "In what bay would you find the Andaman and Nicobar islands?", "answer": "The Bay of Bengal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf4e", "question": "Angelo Sicilano better know as who?", "answer": "Charles Atlas", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c346", "question": "What fluid was the chemical \"taurine\" first derived from?", "answer": "Ox bile", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339426", "question": "What is Sweeny Todd's real name in the 2007 movie by the same name?", "answer": "Benjamin Barker", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adea", "question": "What was the total length of the Berlin Wall?", "answer": "155 km or 96 miles", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be32", "question": "How many players are there in a standard ice hockey team?", "answer": "Six", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5909cab7bb53d1af658864d1", "question": "On what short story was the 1946 film \"It\u2019s a Wonderful Life\" based on?", "answer": "The Greatest Gift", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339260", "question": "What is the stage name of Reginald Kenneth Dwight?", "answer": "Elton John", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b7ff8fc3a3a814d89068c50", "question": "What is the full name of the Shakespearean tragedy \"Hamlet\"?", "answer": "The Tragedy of Hamlet, Prince of Denmark", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af98", "question": "In which war was the Battle of Ramillies?", "answer": "War of Spanish Succession", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399b9", "question": "What actor played the role of Newman in the TV show \"Seinfeld\"?", "answer": "Wayne Knight", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a365", "question": "What country did the Venetian blinds originate in?", "answer": "Persia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59cdb68d65ff7d326b622a97", "question": "The 1980s \"High Society\" was a musical remake of which 1930s play?", "answer": "The Philadelphia Story", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a12b", "question": "Which rockstar is nicknamed Slowhand?", "answer": "Eric Clapton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a99c", "question": "Where would you find the active volcano \"Erebus\"?", "answer": "Antarctica", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133925e", "question": "What country was the movie \"Full Metal Jacket\" filmed in?", "answer": "England", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5be581825415ba52ed6f0ac2", "question": "Who is credited with building the first full-scale working steam locomotive?", "answer": "Richard Trevithick", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae74", "question": "What was the first state to allow women to vote?", "answer": "Wyoming", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59636ed2967692ea851899b4", "question": "What is the Kenny Chesney song about a farm implement?", "answer": "\"She Thinks My Tractor\u2019s Sexy\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "594d07671a1c922dd1ac64b8", "question": "The average adult human has 32 of what?", "answer": "Teeth", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4db", "question": "What do you get when you mix tequila, triple sec and lime juice?", "answer": "A Margarita", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adf1", "question": "The month July is named for what historical leader?", "answer": "Julius Caesar", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2db", "question": "What country was called Northern Rhodesia until 1984?", "answer": "Zambia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58f5671233a95c66dc4fe768", "question": "Who was the third president of the US?", "answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a25f14f6682715b82711cde", "question": "What year was the ice cream cone patented in the US?", "answer": "1903", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c02d", "question": "To determine the percentage of alcohol in a bottle of liquor, what is divided by two?", "answer": "Proof", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339032", "question": "What was the name of Ashley Wilkes' plantation in \"Gone With the Wind\"?", "answer": "Twelve Oaks", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ee8", "question": "What mythical title has been given to poets from Sappho to Anne Bradstreet?", "answer": "The Tenth Muse", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd81f38d0de9af39e9d4694", "question": "What was the highest value of U.S. currency ever put into circulation?", "answer": "$10,000 bill", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6008da4cf4f3bc4a292f8614", "question": "Where was the first commercial winery in the U.S.?", "answer": "Kentucky (Swiss vintner, John James Dufour, chose a spot along the Kentucky River for his vineyards and opened a winery in 1799.)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c756", "question": "In the culinary world, what does MSG short for?", "answer": "Monosodium glutamate", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339892", "question": "Who did Johnny Carson replace as host of \"The Tonight Show\"?", "answer": "Jack Paar", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390ae", "question": "What year did J. D. Salinger publish the novel \"The Catcher in the Rye\"?", "answer": "1951", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff6687952a821ff76ae8b05", "question": "In the Bible, who are Abraham's brothers?", "answer": "Nahor and Haran", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58f564fc33a95c66dc4fe753", "question": "What is the connection between Johnny Logan and Sean Sherrard?", "answer": "They are the same person", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a728", "question": "The Sonoran Desert is located in California and which other state?", "answer": "Arizona", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fef5fc66ce05a3942286e47", "question": "The Kansas City Chiefs were originally known as what?", "answer": "The Dallas Texans", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe4e8f106d333868d34d74f", "question": "Which country's traditional name translates to \"Land of the Thunder Dragon\"?", "answer": "Bhutan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fede4e26ce05a3942286de3", "question": "Who recorded the hit single \"Sussudio\" in 1985?", "answer": "Phil Collins", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c769", "question": "What word describes the enlargement of bone or tissue at the joint between the big toe and the foot?", "answer": "Bunion", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390c5", "question": "What year marked the publishing of Bram Stoker's novel \"Dracula\"?", "answer": "1897", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396d1", "question": "The TV show \"King of the Hill\" was based in what US state?", "answer": "Texas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecc74aec223966ae8f888c", "question": "There have only been five \"quadruple-doubles\" achieved in the NBA. Which player is responsible for two of them?", "answer": "Hakeem Olajuwon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caa2", "question": "With what is sulfur and saltpeter mixed to make gunpowder?", "answer": "Charcoal", "category": "science"}, {"id": "58be2d228faf425cf37add7b", "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Oregon?", "answer": "Salem", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9ce", "question": "What is the lowest point in the United States?", "answer": "Death Valley, California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6015ecfefe83fe1f2a824c06", "question": "How many times are Jews supposed to wash their hands at the Seder table?", "answer": "Two times", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be70", "question": "What is Michigan Stadium also known as?", "answer": "The Big House", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60173c2a44491cbd7c5a17a3", "question": "How did Tuesday get its name?", "answer": "Tuesday is named for the god of war. For the Anglo-Saxons it was Tiu, while the Vikings called him Tyr.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a4d99c808b8581f80b092b7", "question": "What soccer team won the 2017 FIFA Club World Cup?", "answer": "Real Madrid", "category": "general"}]